In order to retrieve this safe from
Suori's mansion, a party has been formed.
Afterwards,
I'll be able to turn into a giant vending
machine and plug the hole in the wall.
There are seven of us,
including me and Lammis.
Between all the rubble along our path, and
trying to avoid any unnecessary combat,
the route's been kinda complicated.
Based on the map, we should be
close once we get through there.
We finally made it to a section
of town, I know. Indeed.
If we follow this path,
we'll see the mansion.
My mansion's in ruins!
Before we came, I thought
I was prepared to see this.
Seeing such a sad look on Suori's
face, I can't even find the words.
It was the first time I've ever seen her
ball like any known child her age would.
On the outside, I'm just a big metal box,
but inside, I've still got a human soul.
In this new world of wonders,
I travel to and fro on the back
of my super strong partner,
Lamas.
The name's Boxo. Hello there.
That means yes, by the way.
I'm not happy with my mood.
If I get something like
that, I'll be right back.
I love it, but I will be right back.
I love it,
but I'll be right back.
I apologize for losing
my composure like that.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Sorry.
The safe should be underground.
Watch your step, everyone.
All this art.
How awful.
To be honest, I expected as much.
The decorations seem
extravagant at first glance,
but they're actually more
affordable than you'd think.
Thank goodness.
Looks like she's back to her usual self.
Here, this way.
Whoa, there's a hidden basement down here?
This is it.
I knew she was rich, but
this is on another level!
Look how much they managed to save!
It's her home.
Why is she surprised?
Is this your first time down here, miss?
I see.
Suori's never actually seen what's
in the basement safe before.
Remind me again.
You're unable to accept
gold bars, right, Boxo? Yes.
In that case, I'll loan you
all the gold coins we have.
Thank yous.
Of course, you're most welcome, dear Boxo.
I'm happy to hear you finally
learned to say my name properly.
Wait a sec.
You can say my name, too, can't you, Boxo?
Yes.
I want to hear it.
Lammis.
You guys heard that, right?
He said it correctly.
Sorry, it's still not perfect.
If only I could say the me part.
If you really listen, he's saying
my name more clearly than yours.
Well, I asked him to call me that.
It's like a secret nickname.
I had forgotten that these
two don't get along very well.
Suori was pretty pushy
when she tried to buy me.
Please, miss, we're short on time.
We should get back to the association.
Yes, yes, I know.
Let me remind you that this is just alone.
As soon as things settle down,
I intend to build the Hunters
Association accordingly.
She's probably trying to
hide her embarrassment.
They say adversity reveals
a person's character.
And it's clear that Suori
is a truly charming person.
They put in 110 gold coins, so
my points increased by 110,000.
That should make the
next step a lot easier.
Hey, we're back!
Can you please give me a comb on Poxel?
No, me too!
He's finally back!
It looks like the heat's
starting to get to them.
Give me some ice.
Everybody, just calm down!
I'll give out ice cream and whatever
else you need, so form a line!
Thankfully that's been dealt with.
But this heat is getting worse by the day.
The residents won't be able to
tolerate this for much longer.
We've got to improve this
situation as soon as possible.
Let's start the meeting with a
discussion on how to repair the wall.
First things first,
with all the money that you've earned,
could you change into your giant form, Boxo?
I could happen for a brief to happen.
How many hours could you maintain it?
One bottle.
In other words, you can hold
it for a single hour, correct?
Win!
I see.
I'm considering ordering
an attack on the enemy
forces once they pull
back for the evening.
That said, if anyone has any
objections, feel free to speak up.
Director, I actually have an idea.
By all means, do tell.
To boost our chance of success,
we'll wait for the enemy
to withdraw and sneak into
a position near the hole
under the cover of darkness.
Then, we'll move on to
the next part of the plan.
Once the monsters launch their
assault on the Hunters Association,
they'll bring as much of
their army as they can muster?
leaving the hole unguarded.
We'll use that to hit them where it hurts.
This is probably our best
chance to fix the wall.
That said, there's one problem.
If we go with your plan, our defenders
will be put in considerable danger.
I know.
I suppose that's a risk
we'll have to take.
You must steal yourselves.
This will likely be a
life-or-death struggle.
The combatants chosen to be part of the
Wall Repair Mission Task Force are Mishuel,
Shirley,
the Band of Gluttons, and Umatei.
Shimelai, three Earth Mages,
and I were the work detail
responsible for fixing the wall.
Voxo's role in the mission
is especially important.
I wish you luck.
This is a lot of
responsibility to place on
a vending machine's
non-existent shoulders.
Though nowadays, vending machines are
expected to work during disasters.
That means I can't let them down.
Karios Gorth,
in the unlikely event we don't return from
our mission, I want you to hold the spot.
Thanks to the provisions
Boxo gave us last night,
you've got enough food to easily
last you at least a month.
Once other strata deal with their
issues, they'll send over reinforcements.
Stay strong.
That's what Director Bear said.
But everyone understood the likelihood of
help coming from the other strata was low.
There are so many of them, that this range
will end up croaked if they notice us.
Seems so.
We could easily kick their tails, but we
should wait for an opening to slip by.
He's right.
We have to wait, and have faith
in those at the association.
I'm a little worried.
I hope Hulemy and the others
are okay. Hello there!
You could have just said, yeah, you know.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
Our reliable gate guards are there, too.
Right.
Sounds like it's begun.
We should go now!
You mustn't be impatient.
I understand how you feel right now.
But we need to wait a little more.
But we...
The voluptuous figure
is as strong as ever.
Director please I'd rather you not
bring up such an embarrassing name.
Based on what director bear said
it sounds like miss shirley used
to be a hunter in the past with
her skills I believe it are you
ready it's time for you to enter
the hole from above and block it
off we're counting on you you the
act boxo I had a feeling that she
wouldn't be happy about me going
in alone good luck in there I
wasn't expecting that so those
sounds just came out I was totally
ready for her to lecture me or try
to stop me from going grandma I
used to say people don't like young
ladies who are too controlling?
so I've decided to have faith in you
and let you do what you think is right.
But that means you have to
come back in working order.
Looks like Lamas is growing up.
I feel pumped knowing she believes in me.
Eat it to me.
Just proud, Boxo. Hello there.
I'd love to wave back but I don't have
any arms so this will have to do for now.
All right I'll be back
There are countless monsters gathering
together from outside the wall.
They're marching in sync.
It's surprising how
coordinated they all are.
Anyway, I don't have time to waste.
Drop point confirmed.
Position check.
Angle check.
Altitude check.
Initiating drop.
Now form change.
Kaboom!
Huh? Huh?
The frog fiends are making a break for it.
Wait a sec.
Could that impact have interrupted whatever
process that was keeping them in line?
If their chain of command is
broken, this is our chance.
Time to use the newest function
I've added to my arsenal.
The vending machine installation
mount concrete slab.
Under normal circumstances, you'd
fix a vending machine in place?
by embedding anchors into a concrete slab.
But we'll skip that part for now
and activate the new function again.
In order to support such a large object,
These concrete slabs are
each over a meter thick.
The hole is only about 10 meters in size,
so I just need to use
this function 10 times.
And like that, the pile is done.
Great! It worked!
Now, go, fight!
You're not getting past me!
Director Bear's going all out, huh?
But the power from this big
frame and those sharp claws...
I kind of feel bad for any
monsters who get in his way.
Hey, Slowpoke, come and catch us!
If you can, that is!
Oh, that must be the roar blessing!
All right, I'd say it's about
our turn now, right, Gramps?
You've got it, Gramps, let's go!
Nice.
Everything's going according to plan.
But it feels like the
monsters are organizing again.
It would make sense if one
of the Netherlord's buddies
was hiding somewhere nearby
and issuing orders to them.
Typically,
a commander would position themselves so
they're safe distance from the front lines.
That said,
they'd still need to have a
good view of the battlefield
and usually have guards
stationed around them.
Though, of course, nobody's
ever that formulaic.
Huh?
There he is, right there.
He's wearing a black robe just how the
Netherlord and the King
of Souls were dressed.
Yeah, not suspicious at all.
Right-o!
I could just crush him as
an ice vending machine,
but if he works for the Netherlord,
we should interrogate him.
Okay.
I'll use my normal form, then.
What's going on?
Huh?
The commander is a human?
I kind of assumed that he'd be a skeleton.
But I guess it's not that strange for some
humans to decide to serve
under the Netherlord.
Where did this blue wall come from?
You there!
Prince of Wallet Freeman!
I can withstand this abuse for a
while, but my points aren't infinite.
Time to end this!
Wait, where the heck is
that voice coming from?
Text-to-speak voice isn't
all that intimidating.
But getting through to
him is what matters.
Stop, please, stop!
Spare my life, I'm begging you!
I can't understand what you're saying!
Please, release me!
Yep, I knew he'd play innocent.
I suppose I'll have to make him
want to tell me the truth then.
Confess to you who acts to deny Hold
on, what are you going to do with that?
What the hell?
I'm well aware that this
is an act of cruelty.
But the lives of the people
I care about are on the line.
I have no choice but to harden my heart.
What did you fake me my mouth
is tingling did you poison me?
Well you can think that
if you'd like but that's
not the worst of it the
true terror has yet to come.
Wait those pills they exploded that liquid
what are you planning on doing with that?
No stop it spamming
don't make me drink that.
Oh no please i'm begging you i don't
want my inside the face that's horrible.
He's more freaked out than i expected.
He's actually in no danger because enough
time has passed since
he drank all that soda.
But he doesn't need to know that.
Yes all right i'll do
whatever you want i'll stop
controlling the monsters just
don't make me think that please.
Well i learned something
new today the threat
from an unknown object
is shockingly effective.
Heed my words remove the
netherlord's bindings.
There.
My control over the
monsters has been released.
What's this?
They're retreating?
I don't understand what's going on.
Master Boxxo!
Hold on, Boxxo!
Are you okay?
Voxo, is this your doing?
And who is this man? The prisoner?
He uses a ring to channel
the Netherlord's power.
I can't even...
Points decreased by 600.
Wait, what's happening?
Points decreased by 404.
Put down the barrier! Boss, no!
If you don't drop it
right now, I'll break it!
I'll smash it to pieces!
What's wrong with Lamas?
She's not acting like her usual self.
Matthew eats.
He has to pay.
If it's the last thing I do, he'll pay!
Stop this! It's him!
That man!
He's the one who used monsters
to destroy my village!
He has to die for what he's done!
Let go!
So that's what's going on.
Please, Lamas. Calm down.
You must get your anger under control.
I understand what you're feeling.
After all the years of anger
and hatred for this man,
and he's finally in front of you?
but you mustn't let your
emotions get the better of you.
This man may have
information that we need.
There are countless people
in other strata who are
suffering and struggling hard
to survive this calamity.
Don't let them experience
the same tragedy.
If you can set aside your desire
for revenge, we can save them.
I hear you.
And you're right.
Sorry, Director Bear.
I'll go repair the wall.
I need some time alone.
Lamis.
Now then you're going to answer all my
questions and tell us what you know.
If you hold anything back I can
promise you won't have an easy death.
If you cooperate and give us a full
confession I'll allow you to die painlessly.
There's no hint of the kind and
gentle director bear that I know.
He's a wild beast who will make
your soul wilt with just a look.
Boxer, could you stay with
Llamas for a little bit?
Don't worry, you can leave
the dirty work to us.
This is something that's
best left to an old hand.
Hello, there!
I don't know what I should
even say to her right now.
I can finally talk in a limited way.
And yet I can't think of
anything worth saying.
Boxxo, forgive me.
All this time, I've wanted to
get revenge from mom and dad,
along with everybody
else from the village.
That's the reason I became
a hunter in the first place,
and tried to get as strong as possible.
That's why, when I saw him there,
my mind went completely blank.
I lost control.
No matter what happens, I
know my place is by her side.
I'll do my best to make
up for anything she lacks.
If her heart is darkened by
sadness, I'll repaint it with joy.
I'll be there for her.
That's my duty as her partner.
With you two, an end.
I hope she understood
what I was trying to say.
I'm not going to let myself die,
so I'll be with you until you quit
being a hunter, or something like that.
Um, Boxxo?
What you just said, did I hear you right?
You want us to get married?
Wait, you definitely
heard me wrong, Lamas.
I'm not against the idea,
but my mother got married to
my father when she was 18,
so ideally I'd like to get hitched
at the same age if possible.
Um, are you listening?
I'm really happy that you proposed, but I
think that it might be a little too soon.
We should get to know
each other better first.
And what can we do about children?
Maybe I could get Hulemy to
make some little boxos for us.
Wouldn't that be cute?
This misunderstanding just
keeps getting worse and worse.
Oh, I know.
We should make our way
to the end of the dungeon
so we can turn you back
into a human being.
I love you the way you are, Boxo, but I'd
really like to see you as a human, too.
And we could do things like hold
hands and go on dates together?
It looks like I threw her for too
much of a loop when she was down,
and now she's confused.
Besides, is romance between a vending
machine and a human even possible?
What am I saying?
I need to calm down!
Just kidding.
I know that you were only trying to
cheer me up because I was feeling upset.
And it worked!
I feel a lot better!
Thanks so much, Boxo!
So Lamas was just messing with me?
I was this close to taking it seriously.
Anyway, it's finally time
to get this wall fixed.
For a second there, I wasn't
sure how things would go.
But it worked out, and Lamas
is in a much better mood now.
Wow!
Take my plane.
This one is changing andzen.
It's never got no altitude anymore.
I'll keep using my passe-luge
Знаing your dzieck.
And right now, move on
myCal improving day.
What time do I take?
You could even win a reward!
I look forward to serving you again!